<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="effects">
        <item>Swap</item>
        <item>Move Zoom Rotate</item>
        <item>Background</item>
        <item>Sketch</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="p_png_tip">
        <item>PNG format will cause </item>
        <item>\"Black Border\"</item>
        <item> after uploaded to social media like Instagram and Facebook.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="cloud_sns_gender_list">
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Male</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="movie_words">
        <item>Have courage and be kind.</item>
        <item>Sometimes we need a little magic.</item>
        <item>Hope is a good thing and maybe the best of things. And no good thing ever dies.</item>
        <item>Get busy living or get busy dying.</item>
        <item>It takes a strong man to save himself, and a great man to save another.</item>
        <item>You got a dream, you gotta protect it.</item>
        <item>"People can't do something themselves, they wanna tell you can't do it."</item>
        <item>"There is an I in \"happiness\", there is no Y in \"happiness\", it's an I."</item>
        <item>"I think it's hard winning a war with words."</item>
        <item>"Sir, you're no gentleman. And you miss are no lady."</item>
        <item>Tomorrow is another day.</item>
        <item>You jump, I jump.</item>
        <item>"We're the luckiest sons-of-bitches in the world."</item>
        <item>All life is a game of luck.</item>
        <item>To make each day count.</item>
        <item>Destiny takes a hand.</item>
        <item>You are my destiny.</item>
        <item>"To eat or not to eat, that's a question."</item>
        <item>When the world turns its back on you. You turn your back on the world.</item>
        <item>"It's you, your scent, it's like a drug to me. You're like my personal brand of heroin."</item>
        <item>Only for making me want you so badly.</item>
        <item>I was unconditionally and irrevocably in love with him.</item>
        <item>Your number was up the first time I met you.</item>
        <item>"You can't change the past."</item>
        <item>"Life was like a box of chocolates, you never know what you're gonna get."</item>
        <item>Miracles happen every day.</item>
        <item>"Money is not everything. There's MasterCard."</item>
        <item>Love is photogenic. It needs darkness to develop.</item>
        <item>"I'd have to lose 60 IQ points to be classified as \"smart\"."</item>
        <item>"I haven't forgotten a single thing since the day my mother stopped breastfeeding me."</item>
        <item>"You don't know good things till they are gone."</item>
        <item>Sunlight creeps in between the curtains.</item>
        <item>"Way to be forgotten.
But that's how you get remembered."</item>
        <item>I love you, always have, always will.</item>
        <item>"There's nothing wrong to keep this secret if its truth will hurt someone."</item>
        <item>"Look, eventually, you'll learn to do that on the inside."</item>
        <item>"I'm a lot of things, but I'm not a quitter."</item>
        <item>"Let's just send out positive energy, and the universe will provide."</item>
        <item>Might as well face it. You and I are on our own.</item>
        <item>"This guy has a brand-new apple. I've been eating the same apple for a week."</item>
        <item>"It's our man-iversary."</item>
        <item>I use the box that our soap comes in as a wallet.</item>
        <item>There is no good and evil, there is only power and those too weak to seek it.</item>
        <item>That suggests that what you fear most of all… is fear itself.</item>
        <item>It is not our abilities that show what we truly are. It is our choices.</item>
        <item>"I'm sorry, professor, but I must not tell lies."</item>
        <item>Behind every great fortune, there is a crime.</item>
        <item>Every man has one destiny.</item>
        <item>You make the choice, and this is your price.</item>
        <item>"Don't let anybody know what you are thinking."</item>
        <item>Life is so beautiful.</item>
        <item>So, love somebody else.</item>
        <item>"Only don't tell me you're innocent. It insults my intelligence, makes me very angry."</item>
        <item>Great people are not born with the great, but in the process of growing up show its great.</item>
        <item>A man who is not a father will never be a real man.</item>
        <item>Do not say impossible, nothing is impossible.</item>
        <item>Whatever can happen, will happen.</item>
        <item>On a scale of 1 to 10, how would you rate your pain?</item>
        <item>There. There.</item>
        <item>Balalalala●—●</item>
        <item>Success is a relative term. It brings so many relatives.</item>
        <item>God made relatives. Thank God we can choose our friends.</item>
        <item>The wise never marry. And when they marry they become otherwise.</item>
        <item>Your future depends on your dreams. So go to sleep.</item>
        <item>There should be a better way to start a day than waking up every morning.</item>
        <item>Hard work never kills anybody. But why take the risk?</item>
        <item>Work fascinates me. I can look at it for hours!</item>
        <item>"Don't let idiots ruin your day."</item>
        <item>I am sorry for what I said when I was hungry.</item>
        <item>"I'm done with Winter! I want to fast-forward to Spring!"</item>
        <item>"Nothing is really lost until Mom can't find it."</item>
        <item>"You can't fix stupid but you can watch it on Facebook every day."</item>
        <item>I never make the same mistake twice. I make it five or six times, just to be sure.</item>
        <item>You were my cup of tea but I drink champagne now.</item>
        <item>I hate two-faced people. I can never decide which side to slap first.</item>
        <item>HOME: Where I can look ugly and enjoy it.</item>
        <item>I may be crazy… but crazy is better than stupid!</item>
        <item>It was you from the moment we met.</item>
        <item>If you want to fly, you have to give up the things that weight you down.</item>
        <item>Every woman is beautiful. Just takes the right man to see it.</item>
        <item>Smile.</item>
        <item>"KEEP CALM! IT'S FRIDAY!"</item>
        <item>"You don't cross my mind.You live on it."</item>
        <item>When I look into your eyes. I tend to lose my thoughts.</item>
        <item>"Fall in love with someone that doesn't make you think love is hard."</item>
        <item>"Sometimes I'm just like…I need a hug!"</item>
        <item>If you are always trying to be NORMAL, you will never know how AMAZING you can be.</item>
        <item>Time is shit.</item>
        <item>Never give up!</item>
        <item>One life ends… another begins.</item>
        <item>Sometimes your whole life boils down to one insane move.</item>
        <item>I see you.</item>
        <item>Welcome to Caribbean!</item>
        <item>"I'm Captain Jack Sparrow."</item>
        <item>"Everything we've ever done has lead to this."</item>
        <item>The only way for a pirate to make a living these days is by betraying other pirates.</item>
        <item>I was nothing more than an almost innocent bystander.</item>
        <item>There will come a moment when you have the chance to do the right thing.</item>
        <item>"Let's put a smile on that face!"</item>
        <item>"It's a funny world we live in, speaking of which, you wanna know how I got these scars?"</item>
        <item>"I believe… whatever doesn't kill you simply makes you… stranger."</item>
        <item>"You know, madness is a lot like gravity…
Sometimes all you need is a little push."</item>
        <item>It does not to do dwell on dreams, and forget to live.</item>
        <item>There are more important things: friendship and bravery.</item>
        <item>"It's not much, but it's home."</item>
        <item>The ones that love us never really leave us. And you can always find them in here.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
