<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="effects">
        <item>交换</item>
        <item>移动 变焦 旋转</item>
        <item>背景</item>
        <item>素描</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="p_png_tip">
        <item>PNG格式在上传到Instagram和Facebook等社交媒体后会产生</item>
        <item>\"黑色边框\"</item>
        <item>。</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="cloud_sns_gender_list">
        <item>女</item>
        <item>男</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="movie_words">
        <item>"坚强而勇敢，仁慈且善良。
Have courage and be kind."</item>
        <item>"有时候，我们需要奇迹。
Sometimes we need a little magic."</item>
        <item>"希望是一个好东西，也许是最好的，好东西是不会消亡的。
Hope is a good thing and maybe the best of things. And no good thing ever dies."</item>
        <item>"汲汲而生，汲汲而死。
Get busy living or get busy dying."</item>
        <item>"坚强的人只能救赎自己，伟大的人才能拯救他人。
It takes a strong man to save himself, and a great man to save another."</item>
        <item>"如果你有梦想，就要守护它。
You got a dream, you gotta protect it."</item>
        <item>"当人们做不到一些事情的时候，他们就会对你说你也同样不能。
People can't do something themselves, they wanna tell you can't do it."</item>
        <item>"幸福里面没有为什么，只有我。
There is an I in \"happiness\", there is no Y in \"happiness\", it's an I."</item>
        <item>"我认为纸上谈兵没什么作用。
I think it's hard winning a war with words."</item>
        <item>"先生，你可真不是个君子，小姐，你也不是什么淑女。
Sir, you're no gentleman. And you miss are no lady."</item>
        <item>"明天又是全新的一天。
Tomorrow is another day."</item>
        <item>"你跳，我跟你跳。
You jump, I jump."</item>
        <item>"我们是真他妈的走运极了。
We're the luckiest sons-of-bitches in the world."</item>
        <item>"生活本来就全靠运气。
All life is a game of luck."</item>
        <item>"要让每一天都有所值。
To make each day count."</item>
        <item>"命中注定。
Destiny takes a hand."</item>
        <item>"你是我的命运。
You are my destiny."</item>
        <item>"吃还是不吃，是需要考虑的问题。
To eat or not to eat, that's a question."</item>
        <item>"如果这个世界对你不理不睬，你也可以这样对待它。
When the world turns its back on you. You turn your back on the world."</item>
        <item>"你，你的气味，对我来说就像海洛因一样无法抗拒。
It's you, your scent, it's like a drug to me. You're like my personal brand of heroin."</item>
        <item>"只有你才能让我如此上瘾。
Only for making me want you so badly."</item>
        <item>"我不顾一切地爱上了他。
I was unconditionally and irrevocably in love with him."</item>
        <item>"我第一次遇见你的时候你就劫数难逃。
Your number was up the first time I met you."</item>
        <item>"过去的事是不可以改变的。
You can't change the past."</item>
        <item>"生命就像一盒巧克力，结果往往出人意料。
Life was like a box of chocolates, you never know what you're gonna get."</item>
        <item>"奇迹每天都在发生。
Miracles happen every day."</item>
        <item>"钞票不是万能的，有时还需要信用卡。
Money is not everything. There's MasterCard."</item>
        <item>"爱情就像照片，需要大量的暗房时间来培养。
Love is photogenic. It needs darkness to develop."</item>
        <item>"要被归为“聪明人”我得去掉60点智商才行。
I'd have to lose 60 IQ points to be classified as \"smart\"."</item>
        <item>"从我妈给我断奶后我就没忘掉过一件事。
I haven't forgotten a single thing since the day my mother stopped breastfeeding me."</item>
        <item>"有些东西失去了才懂得珍惜。
You don't know good things till they are gone."</item>
        <item>"阳光穿过窗。
Sunlight creeps in between the curtains."</item>
        <item>"被人遗忘，也是被人记起的方法。
Way to be forgotten. But that's how you get remembered."</item>
        <item>"我爱你，一直是，永远会。
I love you, always have, always will."</item>
        <item>"如果真相伤人，那保守秘密就没什么不对。
There's nothing wrong to keep this secret if its truth will hurt someone."</item>
        <item>"终有一天，你会学会泪往心里流。
Look, eventually, you'll learn to do that on the inside."</item>
        <item>"我虽然不是什么好人，但绝对不是缩头乌龟。
I'm a lot of things, but I'm not a quitter."</item>
        <item>"我们只要散发正能量，宇宙会证明给我们看的。
Let's just send out positive energy, and the universe will provide."</item>
        <item>"还是面对现实吧，我们要靠自己。
Might as well face it. You and I are on our own."</item>
        <item>"这家伙还有台新苹果，而我却一周都在吃同一个苹果。
This guy has a brand-new apple. I've been eating the same apple for a week."</item>
        <item>"今天可是我们的基念日啊！
It's our man-iversary."</item>
        <item>"我都穷到拿肥皂盒当钱包了。
I use the box that our soap comes in as a wallet."</item>
        <item>"世上并没有绝对的善与恶，差别只在于强者和无法分清事实的弱者。
There is no good and evil, there is only power and those too weak to seek it."</item>
        <item>"你最恐惧的其实是恐惧本身。
That suggests that what you fear most of all… is fear itself."</item>
        <item>"决定我们成为什么样人的，不是我们的能力，而是我们的选择。
It is not our abilities that show what we truly are. It is our choices."</item>
        <item>"对不起，教授，我不可以说谎。
I'm sorry, professor, but I must not tell lies."</item>
        <item>"巨大财富的背后，都隐藏着罪恶。
Behind every great fortune, there is a crime."</item>
        <item>"一个人只有一个命运。
Every man has one destiny."</item>
        <item>"你做出了这个决定，这是你的代价。
You make the choice, and this is your price."</item>
        <item>"永远不要让别人知道你的真实想法。
Don't let anybody know what you are thinking."</item>
        <item>"生活是如此的美丽。
Life is so beautiful."</item>
        <item>"那么，去爱一些其他人吧。
So, love somebody else."</item>
        <item>"这个世界本身就没有所谓的清白而言。你敢说，你从来就没说过慌？这是自欺欺人。
Only don't tell me you're innocent. It insults my intelligence, makes me very angry."</item>
        <item>"伟大的人不是生下来就伟大的，而是在成长过程中显示其伟大的。
Great people are not born with the great, but in the process of growing up show its great."</item>
        <item>"不顾家庭的男人不是真正的男人。
A man who is not a father will never be a real man."</item>
        <item>"不要说不可能，没有什么不可能。
Do not say impossible, nothing is impossible."</item>
        <item>"该发生的事总会发生。
Whatever can happen, will happen."</item>
        <item>"从1到10，你的疼痛指数有多少？
On a scale of 1 to 10, how would you rate your pain?"</item>
        <item>"乖啊。乖。
There. There."</item>
        <item>"成功是一个相关名词，他会给你带来很多不相关的亲戚（联系）。
Success is a relative term. It brings so many relatives."</item>
        <item>"上天决定了你的出身，幸运的是在选择朋友方面给你留了余地。
God made relatives.Thank God we can choose our friends."</item>
        <item>"聪明人都是未婚的，结婚的人很难再聪明起来。
The wise never marry. And when they marry they become otherwise."</item>
        <item>"现在的梦想决定着你的将来，所以还是再睡一会吧。
Your future depends on your dreams. So go to sleep."</item>
        <item>"应该有更好的方式开始新一天，而不是千篇一律的在每个上午都醒来。
There should be a better way to start a day than waking up every morning."</item>
        <item>"努力工作不会导致死亡！不过干嘛要冒这个险？
Hard work never kills anybody. But why take the risk?"</item>
        <item>"工作好有意思耶！尤其是看着别人工作。
Work fascinates me. I can look at it for hours!"</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
