<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="effects">
        <item>交換</item>
        <item>移動 變焦 旋轉</item>
        <item>背景</item>
        <item>素描</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="p_png_tip">
        <item>PNG格式在上傳到Instagram和Facebook等社交媒體後會產生</item>
        <item>\"黑色邊框\"</item>
        <item>。</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="cloud_sns_gender_list">
        <item>女</item>
        <item>男</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="movie_words">
        <item>"堅強而勇敢，仁慈且善良。
Have courage and be kind."</item>
        <item>"有時候，我們需要奇跡。
Sometimes we need a little magic."</item>
        <item>"希望是一個好東西，也許是最好的，好東西不會消亡。
Hope is a good thing and maybe the best of things. And no good thing ever dies."</item>
        <item>"汲汲而生，汲汲而死。
Get busy living or get busy dying."</item>
        <item>"堅強的人只能救贖自己，偉大的人才能拯救他人。
It takes a strong man to save himself, and a great man to save another."</item>
        <item>"如果你有夢想，就要守護它。
You got a dream, you gotta protect it."</item>
        <item>"當人們做不到一些事情的時候，他們就會對你說你也同樣不能。
People can't do something themselves, they wanna tell you can't do it."</item>
        <item>"幸福裏面沒有為什麽，只有我。
There is an I in \"happiness\", there is no Y in \"happiness\", it's an I."</item>
        <item>"我認為紙上談兵沒什麽作用。
I think it's hard winning a war with words."</item>
        <item>"先生，你可真不是個君子，小姐，你也不是什麽淑女。
Sir, you're no gentleman. And you miss are no lady."</item>
        <item>"明天又是全新的一天。
Tomorrow is another day."</item>
        <item>"你跳，我跟你跳。
You jump, I jump."</item>
        <item>"我們真他媽的走運極了。
We're the luckiest sons-of-bitches in the world."</item>
        <item>"生活本來就全靠運氣。
All life is a game of luck."</item>
        <item>"要讓每一天都有所值。
To make each day count."</item>
        <item>"命中註定。
Destiny takes a hand."</item>
        <item>"你是我的命運。
You are my destiny."</item>
        <item>"吃還是不吃，是需要考慮的問題。
To eat or not to eat, that's a question."</item>
        <item>"如果這個世界對你不理不睬，你也可以這樣對待它。
When the world turns its back on you. You turn your back on the world."</item>
        <item>"你，你的氣味，對我來說就像海洛因一樣無法抗拒。
It's you, your scent, it's like a drug to me. You're like my personal brand of heroin."</item>
        <item>"只有你才能讓我如此上癮。
Only for making me want you so badly."</item>
        <item>"我不顧一切地愛上了他。
I was unconditionally and irrevocably in love with him."</item>
        <item>"我第一次遇見你的時候你就劫數難逃。
Your number was up the first time I met you."</item>
        <item>"過去的事是不可以改變的。
You can't change the past."</item>
        <item>"生命就像一盒巧克力，結果往往出人意料。
Life was like a box of chocolates, you never know what you're gonna get."</item>
        <item>"奇蹟每天都在發生。
Miracles happen every day."</item>
        <item>"鈔票不是萬能的，有時還需要信用卡。
Money is not everything. There's MasterCard."</item>
        <item>"愛情就像照片，需要大量的暗房時間來培養。
Love is photogenic. It needs darkness to develop."</item>
        <item>"要被歸為“聰明人”我得去掉60點智商才行。
I'd have to lose 60 IQ points to be classified as \"smart\"."</item>
        <item>"從我媽給我斷奶後我就沒忘掉過一件事。
I haven't forgotten a single thing since the day my mother stopped breastfeeding me."</item>
        <item>"有些東西失去了才懂得珍惜。
You don't know good things till they are gone."</item>
        <item>"陽光穿過窗。
Sunlight creeps in between the curtains."</item>
        <item>"被人遺忘，也是被人記起的方法。
Way to be forgotten. But that's how you get remembered."</item>
        <item>"我愛你，一直是，永遠會。
I love you, always have, always will."</item>
        <item>"如果真相傷人，那保守秘密就沒什麼不對。
There's nothing wrong to keep this secret if its truth will hurt someone."</item>
        <item>"終有一天，你會學會淚往心裡流。
Look, eventually, you'll learn to do that on the inside."</item>
        <item>"我雖然不是什麼好人，但絕對不是縮頭烏龜。
I'm a lot of things, but I'm not a quitter."</item>
        <item>"我們只要散發正能量，宇宙會證明給我們看的。
Let's just send out positive energy, and the universe will provide."</item>
        <item>"面對現實吧，我們要靠自己。
Might as well face it. You and I are on our own."</item>
        <item>"這傢伙還有台新蘋果，而我卻一周都在吃同一個蘋果。
This guy has a brand-new apple. I've been eating the same apple for a week."</item>
        <item>"今天是我們的基念日啊！
It's our man-iversary."</item>
        <item>"我都窮到拿肥皂盒當錢包了。
I use the box that our soap comes in as a wallet."</item>
        <item>"世上並沒有絕對的善與惡，差別只在於強者和無法分清事實的弱者。
There is no good and evil, there is only power and those too weak to seek it."</item>
        <item>"你最恐懼的其實是恐懼本身。
That suggests that what you fear most of all… is fear itself."</item>
        <item>"決定我們成為什麼樣人的，不是我們的能力，而是我們的選擇。
It is not our abilities that show what we truly are, it is our choices."</item>
        <item>"對不起，教授，我不可以說謊。
I'm sorry, professor, but I must not tell lies."</item>
        <item>"巨大財富的背後，都隱藏著罪惡。
Behind every great fortune, there is a crime."</item>
        <item>"一個人只有一個命運。
Every man has one destiny."</item>
        <item>"你做出了這個決定，這是你的代價。
You make the choice, and this is your price."</item>
        <item>"永遠不要讓別人知道你的真實想法。
Don't let anybody know what you are thinking."</item>
        <item>"生活是如此的美麗。
Life is so beautiful."</item>
        <item>"那麼，去愛一些其他人吧。
So, love somebody else."</item>
        <item>"這個世界本身就沒有所謂的清白而言。你敢說，你從來就沒說過慌？這是自欺欺人。
Only don't tell me you're innocent. It insults my intelligence, makes me very angry."</item>
        <item>"偉大的人不是生下來就偉大的，而是在成長過程中顯示其偉大的。
Great people are not born with the great, but in the process of growing up show its great."</item>
        <item>"不顧家的男人不是真正的男人。
A man who is not a father will never be a real man."</item>
        <item>"不要說不可能，沒有什麼不可能。
Do not say impossible, nothing is impossible."</item>
        <item>"該發生的事總會發生。
Whatever can happen, will happen."</item>
        <item>"從1到10，你的疼痛指數有多少？
On a scale of 1 to 10, how would you rate your pain?"</item>
        <item>"乖啊。乖。
There. There."</item>
        <item>"成功是一個相關名詞，他會給你帶來很多不相關的親戚。
Success is a relative term. It brings so many relatives."</item>
        <item>"上天決定了你的出身，幸運的是在選擇朋友方面給你留了余地。
God made relatives.Thank God we can choose our friends."</item>
        <item>"聰明人都是未婚的，結婚的人很難再聰明起來。
The wise never marry. And when they marry they become otherwise."</item>
        <item>"現在的夢想決定著你的將來，所以還是再睡一會吧。
Your future depends on your dreams. So go to sleep."</item>
        <item>"應該有更好的方式開始新一天，而不是千篇一律的在每個上午醒來。
There should be a better way to start a day than waking up every morning."</item>
        <item>"努力工作不會導致死亡！不過乾嘛要冒這個險。
Hard work never kills anybody. But why take the risk?"</item>
        <item>"工作好有意思耶！尤其是看著別人工作。
Work fascinates me. I can look at it for hours!"</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
